<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="root_existingWallet_restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="restore_subtitle">Seed Recovery Phrase</string>
    <string name="restoreWallet_info">Please type in your 24-word secret recovery phrase in the correct order.</string>
    <string name="general_next">Next</string>

    <string name="restore_dialog_message_1_bold_part">The Secret Recovery Phrase</string>
    <string name="restore_dialog_message_1">is a unique set of 24 words, appearing in a
        precise order. It can be used to gain full control of your funds from any device via any Zcash wallet app.
        Think of it as the master key to your wallet. It is stored in Zodl’s Advanced Settings.</string>
    <string name="restore_dialog_message_2_bold_part">The Wallet Birthday Height</string>
    <string name="restore_dialog_message_2">is the block height (block # in the
        blockchain) at which your wallet was created. If you ever lose access to your Zodl app and need to recover
        your funds, providing the block height along with your recovery phrase can significantly speed up the process.
    </string>

    <string name="restoreWallet_birthday_estimate">Estimate my block height</string>

    <string name="firstWalletTransactionSubtitleRestore">Decide how far Zodl should scan. Enter a date before your first received transaction. If you\’re not sure, choose an earlier date.</string>

    <string name="restore_seed_warning_suggestions">This word is not in the seed phrase dictionary.  Please select the correct one from the suggestions.</string>

    <string name="torSettingsSheet_msg">If Tor is available in your region, we recommend enabling it for enhanced privacy during wallet restoration. This step is completely optional.</string>
    <string name="torSettingsSheet_desc">Routes your connection through the Tor network for enhanced anonymity and privacy protection.</string>

    <string name="firstWalletTransactionSubtitleResync">Decide how far Zodl should resync. Enter a date before your first received transaction. If you\'re not sure, choose an earlier date.</string>

    <string name="resync_bd_estimation_message">Your wallet will be resynced from %1$s (%2$s blocks). Zodl will scan and recover all transactions made after the following block number.</string>
    <string name="resyncWallet_confirmTitle">Confirm Resync</string>
    <string name="confirm_resync_subtitle">Resync the current wallet without resetting the app. This can be used to
        troubleshoot issues that would normally require restoring your wallet like fixing your Keystone
        balance.\n\nUnless you specify otherwise below, Zodl will resync from the date displayed.</string>
    <string name="resyncWallet_dateInfo">Unless you specify otherwise below, Zodl will resync from the date displayed.</string>
    <string name="confirm_resync_info">Your wallet will be resynced from %1$s (%2$s blocks). Use the button below if you wish to change it.</string>
    <string name="resyncWallet_change">Change</string>

    <string name="resyncWallet_failedTitle">Resync Failed</string>
    <string name="resyncWallet_failedDescription">Resync of the wallet couldn’t be finalized. Please try again or report an issue.</string>

</resources>
